(This program contains indirect advertisements.)
Why don't we go to a karaoke room and get the energy up?
Sure. Let's do it.
(The night in Tongyeong grows deeper.)
Why don't we sing for just one hour?
- Okay, 1 hour would be enough.
- Seriously, just 1 hour.
Let's have fun for an hour.
- Oh, my.
- Hello.
Hello.
- We're here to sing.
- Sure.
- Welcome.
- Hello.
I'll give you 5 dollars. I have a 5-dollar bill.
- You have it?
- Yes, here you go.
You may go to Blue Crab Room.
For Blue Crab Room, go to the side.
This karaoke room has all kinds of things.
(Packed with items)
Jung Ah, do you want a matching set with me?
- That way, we can sing together.
- Yes.
- I'll go later.
- Really?
(Giant bow sisters)
That looks cute.
(Each of them puts on one item.)
- Keep it more to the front.
- Okay.
- Thank you.
- Let's go to Blue Crab Room.
(Heading to Blue Crab Room)
Press the start button.
- Are you going to start?
- Press start.
- Okay.
- I will...
It's a little embarrassing to sing in front of you.
(He felt a lot of pressure for his karaoke debut.)
(Will he be able to pull it off?)
I will start.
I don't usually go to karaoke bars.
Since I'm in front of you, I'll put on a little show.
(Let's start You Soon's talent show.)
When I happened to see you
(A sudden change)
(Why did he even worry?)
Those eyes of yours
(They're captivated right away.)
(There's something I want to tell you)
(Puppy Kang is also good at singing.)
(Feeling proud of him)
(Boom, clap)
(Exclaiming)
(Taking over the stage)
(The youngest is also having a blast.)
(Fool)
(I must be a fool)
(Dance time, let's go!)
(Step to the left, step to the right)
(Wiggling)
Oh, my.
This is what he was setting us up for.
- I hardly ever sing.
- He said that he was a bad singer.
(Why did I say that?)
Look at him.
(He was born to be a karaoke star.)
My gosh.
(You Seok's debut performance is a huge success.)
- That was insane.
- Seriously...
That was cute.
- That was insane.
- I don't sing just anywhere.
By the way...
Gosh.
- The headband looks great on you.
- I agree.
It looks perfect on you.
- "A Flower Yet to Bloom?" - The youngest is good.
It's been over ten years...
since I last came to karaoke.
- That's great.
- It's been over ten years.
(Shyly making his way onto the stage)
Are you not coming?
(His voice is great,)
(and the vibes are good.)
(Casually)
(Slipping his hand in his pocket)
(Packing every ounce of middle-aged emotion into the performance)
(Upon a bare, lonely branch)
(His deeply emotional voice has everyone tearing up.)
(Jingling)
(Alone, trying to make a single flower bloom)
(Are you trembling in sorrow?)
(Even the bird that cried along with you grows weary)
(Exploding with emotions)
(He definitely has a story.)
(At his anguished cry,)
(the audience is also getting teary.)
(I'll make that one unbloomed flower finally bloom)
(Giving it everything for the finale)
- He's a good singer.
- He's good.
- He's very good at singing.
- You're amazing.
(He destroyed that stage.)
(The lingering afterglow)
(It's time to shake things up after the ballad song.)
(Following the entertainment director, Yoon Seo)
(Raise the energy!)
(Because I'm a cruel woman)
(Screaming)
(The art student is killing it.)
(Forever)
(This is her ending pose.)
Well done.
(Our youngest is doing well.)
(Throwing in "TTL" since she's good)
(She's not swimming.)
(The youngest can rap too.)
(In case I see you, in case you come back)
(After finishing the 1st verse with a bang)
Cancel it.
- I still love you...
- Oh, my.
(I still love you)
(The song stops.)
(Embarrassed)
(I'm so sorry.)
I guess the song is over
(Feeling awkward)
I must be flustered
(Who is this man?)
How can our timing be this bad?
I guess we're not meant to be
(Let's enjoy a little more of the youngest ones' talent show)
(Yoon Seo is filming him.)
(Yoon Seo's camera)
(Nostalgic)
(Yoon Seo is being filmed this time.)
(Hae Joon's camera)
(Here we have a coming-of-age movie.)
(Peekaboo)
(The siblings have a wonderful time.)
(They even sang along to AKMU songs they had been singing all day.)
(On cloudy days)
(On sunny days)
I think I lost my voice from singing.
- That was so much fun.
- We really made the most...
- of our day.
- The day was very long.
(With a promise to keep having fun, they wrap up the day.)
Hae Joon is...
quite special.
You met him for the first time, but don't you feel...
- comfortable around him?
- I do.
- Isn't it strangely comfortable?
- Exactly.
- Isn't it strange?
- Yes.
I'm so glad that you're here.
For you,
I'd come anytime.
The three of us were in "Love, Take Two."
(They co-starred in "Love, Take Two.")
- You played You Seok's dad.
- Right.
It'd be strange...
- if you hadn't come.
- Right.
(It was impossible for him not to come.)
If Jung Ah asked anyone...
to come, they'd all come.
- It's quite amazing.
- Yes.
- You mean, Jung Ah?
(That's the charm of Captain Yum.)
When I was invited to this show,
- I also came here for Jung Ah.
- I said yes without looking back.
- It was because of Jung Ah.
- I came here because of you.
- But it's over.
- Right, I came here for you too.
I had never seen you, but...
- But it's over.
You're right. I almost forgot.
Jung Ah wasn't that important.
- I came here for You Seok.
- Me too.
I came here for You Seok. When I found out about him,
I said, "I'll definitely go."
(Just then, Captain Yum comes back.)
- It's not about catching something.
- We'll catch flatfish.
- It's just a ride.
- It's a ride.
It's for You Seok to have fun.
- No.
- Can't we ride the boat at 10am?
I don't need to ride it again. I already did it.
Then why are you sticking out your lips?
We already rode the boat. This time...
But you keep sticking out your lower lip.
- Why does it keep sticking out?
- That's not true.
I'm serious this time.
I saw him from a 90° angle.
- You Seok does everything he wants.
- No way.
- His cuteness as his weapon.
- But I love it.
I love that you all let me do whatever I want.
This isn't a place where...
you get to check off your bucket list.
I did everything. I went luge riding, and I drove a boat.
I accomplished everything on my list.
The last one up is Kang You Seok.
I don't want to wash up.
- You Seok, dry your hair.
- I never dry my hair.
- That's cool.
- Jung Ah.
Why don't you tell me to dry my hair?
- You haven't dried your hair?
- I tied it up right away.
- Don't tie it up while it's wet.
- You shouldn't do that.
He and I are the same.
- No, you should dry your hair.
- Sun Young.
- Why not?
- What's wrong with him?
Your hair isn't as long as hers.
Your hair is short. Why is it not okay?
It's definitely not okay. You need to dry your scalp first.
It's bad for your hair and scalp.
It's bad for your scalp.
This is for sure.
(They're two peas in a pod.)
My goodness.
Let's go to bed.
- We should.
- Let's sleep.
We need sleep for tomorrow.
Sleep well.
- Good night.
- Sleep well.
(As the hiding sun slowly peeks its head out)
(Morning arrives in Sopo Village.)
(Some already started their day early.)
(Cats...)
(and magpies welcome the morning in their own ways.)
(It's time for the siblings to wake up.)
(But the house is completely quiet.)
(They had promised to take the outboard boat at 7am.)
(Yet there's no sign of the two of them getting up.)
(Just then, Jung Ah gets up.)
(Did the boys leave?)
(Knocking)
Gosh, they're still here.
- What?
- Aren't you going to work out?
- Work out?
- Aren't you going on the boat?
- You Seok.
- Hey.
(She wakes up You Seok who's still sleeping.)
My goodness.
They aren't up yet.
I guess they slept through.
They were supposed to leave at 7am, but they're still in bed.
(She goes right back to dreamland.)
(The two of them are still half asleep.)
I'll take a shower when we get back.
(While Hae Joon goes to shower first,)
(You Seok gets up.)
(Opening up the curtains)
(He even neatly makes the bed.)
(After washing up, he puts on sunscreen.)
- Let's go.
(They're ready to head out.)
Are you taking your jacket with you?
- It's cold when you're at the sea.
- No, it's not.
- Goodness.
- It's not cold. I'm serious.
(They start bickering from the moment they leave.)
How much fun could riding a boat be?
I want to give you a boat ride.
You've only been on a boat with my older sister.
(In the drama, Hae Joon only went on a boat with his daughter.)
Were you disappointed by that?
(He doesn't deny it.)
Eun Myeong.
- Yes, Father.
- Don't be disappointed.
(Simple)
Gosh, the water is clear.
- What?
- The water is clear.
Yes, it's very clear.
How can the seawater be this clear?
(It's so clear you can see all the way to the bottom.)
(There are also winkles living here.)
(With excitement, they head out to get on the boat.)
(Buckling their seat belts)
Did you put on your seat belt?
- Here we go.
- Yes, let's go.
Let's go.
The weather is beautiful. Even the smell...
(Under the sunlight that sparkles even more brightly today,)
(the peaceful scenery passes by outside the window.)
(Father and son happily set off on a little date of their own.)
So this is what it feels like to have your son drive you around.
It's touching.
(Watching his son drive somehow brings a lump to his throat.)
When did he become an adult?
(When did my son grow up so much?)
This is great.
(I'm loving this moment.)
He's driving for me and taking me out on the boat.
- I'll take you everywhere.
- Yes.
(His son is giving up the full treatment.)
You've done your duty as a good son.
(Smiling)
(As they continue down the road,)
(the blue sea comes into view on the right.)
My goodness.
(Staring)
How is the water so clear? It's the sea.
It's fascinating.
(Now matter how many times you look,)
(the clear ocean is breathtaking.)
(They can't stop marvelling at it.)
- Isn't it beautiful?
- The view is magnificent.
(After taking in the brilliant blue sea and deep green landscape)
We're here.
(They finally arrive at the outboard boat dock.)
- Are we here?
- Yes.
"Water sports place?"
- This is...
- We can get out.
(I'll guide you once you get out.)
Hello.
Did you enjoy it last time?
I came back with my father this time.
- I see.
- Your father?
(They put on their life jackets and fasten the strap.)
- Do you want to fish?
- Sure.
- You want to?
- Yes.
(Today, they're also planning to go fishing.)
(As these outboard boats are easy to operate without a boating license,)
(many people drive them out to their preferred fishing spots...)
(and enjoy fishing from that boat.)
Do you know how to fish?
You just cast it.
(Fishing is just casting.)
(He boards the boat with confident steps.)
Hey, this is...
(Being careful)
Once we go...
- Do you want to operate it?
- No.
Operating it is easier than you think.
Are you...
(Fully at ease on his 2nd time on an outboard boat)
- Shall we set out now?
- Are you...
going to operate it?
It'll just be the two of us.
- Seriously?
- Yes.
This is great.
Captain.
Let's go.
(I'll make sure you're taken care of.)
(Captain Kang is getting more skilled at driving it.)
Let's go.
Father, let's go and catch some fish.
(They set off with dreams of returning with a boat full of fish.)
(Exclaiming)
I didn't think you'd operate the boat.
- You didn't know?
- No.
You thought that someone else would drive it?
That's not fun.
Gosh, this is great.
(Having You Seok drive makes it even more fun.)
All right.
Gosh, this is good.
(They power through the deep blue sea.)
The water is very calm.
(As they take in the scenery around them)
Shall we fish over here?
- Is this a fishing spot?
- Yes.
Do you know how to fish?
Don't you just throw it in...
(Full of confidence)
And catch fish?
(They both try putting some bait on their hooks.)
(Glancing)
(A long, dangling earthworm)
You've never been fishing before, have you?
- What?
- You can't hook it on like that.
- You think so, right?
- Yes.
You've never been fishing, have you?
(Goodness)
It shouldn't be too short.
Fish will bite it off and leave.
(This won't work, You Seok.)
(I'll show you what fishing is about.)
(He's throwing it.)
(What?)
(The fishing line comes loose before he gets a proper casting.)
(Flustered)
This is...
Gosh.
(Shooing off)
(It looks like it landed somewhere up ahead.)
- How do I undo it?
- That...
(The bait goes in and comes right back out.)
Let me see.
(Their first casts end in anticlimactic failure.)
Aren't we supposed to cast it way out there?
But we're only beginners.
(Being very honest)
It'd be nice to catch some fish.
(It's a big dream for beginners.)
There's no fish.
You haven't waited long enough.
Aren't you supposed to catch it fast?
Of course not.
Is this a spot without fish?
(In 2 minutes, he already gets impatient.)
Just wait.
It isn't as easy as you think.
Should we get closer to that island?
You cast it not so long ago.
(Fishing is all about staying in your seat.)
(Getting up)
(Yet he moves immediately to another spot.)
(Moving again)
(Moving three times)
Goodness.
(His butt isn't heavy enough.)
I don't think we'll catch any.
I was worried that we'd catch too much.
- What? Seriously?
- What if we catch too much?
Fishing isn't as easy as I thought.
(Meanwhile, at home,)
(the youngest is up and getting ready.)
(Grunting)
They went for a boat ride.
(Laughing)
The two of them are hilarious.
(The whole situation is just too funny.)
They're going to fish.
On that boat?
Who goes fishing on that boat?
It's impossible.
(We do.)
(Putting their worries aside, they laugh at the thought of them.)
(Shall we start the day?)
It's time to get up.
Okay.
(Still half asleep, she staggers off to wash up.)
What's this?
I should've started the washing machine.
(The morning officially begins.)
(Whoosh)
Goodness.
(The youngest immediately starts making the bed.)
You're doing well.
- I'm doing well.
- You're doing well.
(Encouraged by Jung Ah's praise, she picks up the pace.)
All right.
There we go.
(The bed is made in no time.)
(Surprised)
- Thank you.
- Yoon Seo did it all.
(Smiling at the youngest's sweet little gesture)
(Hae Joon and You Seok still haven't caught a single fish.)
I guess there's no fish here.
- There's no fish here.
- What?
There's no fish here.
- Shall we go, father?
- Let's go.
(After 30 minutes, they give up fishing.)
Where should I hang it?
We should've caught one.
It's impossible.
- I'll turn the boat around.
- Let's go.
(Let's go back home.)
Gosh, the weather is beautiful.
- Father.
- Yes?
Are you liking it?
Keep going straight.
This is great.
(They may have caught nothing, but they're still positive.)
Can't we take this boat...
all the way to the port in front of our house?
- I see.
- All the way to our house.
The sea must be connected.
Of course it is.
Shall we give it a go?
(The outboard boat can only be operated in designated areas.)
The boat ride is a lot of fun.
Right?
Aren't you glad that you came?
I like it.
(A memorable date for the two of them)
What shall we have for breakfast?
We'll make seaweed pot rice with seaweed we got yesterday.
I've never made pot rice before,
so there's a chance that I mess it up.
Jung Ah, it will still be delicious.
(What Jung Ah makes is guaranteed to be good.)
Just in case I mess it up,
I'll also make delicious green onion yukgaejang.
(Breakfast item 2: Green onion yukgaejang)
This way.
(From the vast Geoje sea in the southern coast)
(They painstakingly hauled up with a 9.3-meter pulling rake.)
(Gyeonnaeryang’s seasonal specialty, wild rock seaweed)
(How about making breakfast with this precious wild seaweed?)
We need...
to set up two burners.
- The fire? Okay.
- You know...
(The youngest is in charge of fire today instead of You Seok.)
(Lifting easily)
(Like a true teto-girl, she handles the heavy burner with ease.)
(Wide apart)
This isn't necessary.
(She sets the burner down in a powerful stance.)
(The bricks to protect against the heat are lined up perfectly.)
This is exhausting.
It must've been hard for You Seok.
(Even when it gets tough,)
(she never overlooks the little details.)
(While Yoon Seo gets the burners ready)
All right.
I'll prepare the vegetables again.
(Sun Young starts washing ingredients by the outdoor sink.)
We won't eat a lot for breakfast.
(She takes time to chat with the viewers.)
So I'll wash three of them.
Viewers, doesn't it look refreshing?
It's best to wash it like giving a rinse on the neck.
To remove all the pesticides, you must soak it...
for about ten minutes. I told you yesterday.
But we don't have enough time.
You can just rinse it...
(A handy washing tip when you're short on time)
Under a strong stream of water.
(Laughing)
It's all washed.
Next is mung bean sprouts.
(It's time to wash mung bean sprouts next.)
Jung Ah, do you need all these mung bean sprouts?
No.
Shouldn't I still rinse them all?
- No.
- No?
Just rinse enough for today's breakfast.
Then I'll wash one-third of the bag.
One-third of mung bean sprouts.
About this much.
Is it too much? Oh, no. It's too much.
Mung bean sprouts...
(The veggie-washing expert's solution for this situation is...)
are good for your health. Let's eat a lot of them.
Wash them like this.
(Hose down the mung bean sprouts as well.)
That's it. I'm done with the mung bean sprouts.
(She's finished washing the mung bean sprouts too.)
Next...
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
Should I shred the oyster mushroom?
Yes, but I won't use all of it.
- You won't use all of it?
- No, it's too much.
Jung Ah, then I will prepare just half.
(With Chef Yum's approval, she'll prepare only half.)
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
How many chilli peppers should I wash?
Just wash all of them.
(Please stop asking me. I'm tired.)
Jung Ah, how big should I chop this?
- Just like the ones I chopped.
- Got it.
(She has to answer both Sun Young and Yoon Seo at the same time.)
Jung Ah must be tired because we keep asking her questions.
(Their questions leave the leader completely overwhelmed.)
(Smiling)
This is why it's so hard to be a leader.
Just following orders is the easiest.
(Jung Ah already looks exhausted before she even starts cooking.)
I'll tidy up here later.
(Thanks to all her questions, she finished washing the ingredients.)
Jang Geum, is it going well?
- Of course.
- Good.
(Yoon Seo suddenly turned into Jang Geum.)
- You chop the green onion.
- This is a piece of cake.
Mommy will...
chop the chilli peppers.
(Jang Geum and her mother chop vegetables, sitting side by side.)
What are the chilli peppers for?
Are these for green onion yukgaejang?
- Does she need this much...
- For green onion yukgaejang?
I guess it needs this much.
(She's Jang Geum's mother, but she's not a good cook.)
(She still has the look of a cooking expert.)
Okay. I'm done.
I'm done. It's all done.
(She finished chopping chilli peppers in a flash.)
I chopped all of them.
(Glancing)
(Jang Geum still has a lot of green onion left to chop.)
Let me help you with whatever you need.
(She brings some of the green onion to help her daughter.)
(Chopping the green onion quickly)
You don't need to chop the green part like that.
Oh, my. Okay.
Done.
(Thanks to the fast-working mother, the green onion is ready too.)
Done. What should I do now, Jung Ah?
Nothing. Just rest now.
- "Nothing?" - I can just rest?
You can set the table or something.
Do whatever you need to. Just don't ask me any questions.
- Okay.
- Got it.
Don't ask her any questions.
- Find something to do on your own.
- Don't ask her any questions.
- You kept asking her questions.
- We shouldn't bother our leader.
Make sure to leave her alone. I heard you asking her questions.
- Okay. Let's stay quiet.
- And don't talk to her.
- She needs to focus now.
- Right.
- She's sensitive right now.
- Now, I'm going to...
I should tidy things up now.
(She always does what Jung Ah says.)
(Meanwhile, Jung Ah has to make two dishes,)
(which are green onion yukgaejang and wild rock seaweed pot rice.)
- Sun Young.
- Yes?
Check if the pot is hot enough...
and cook the meat...
- Should I stir-fry the meat?
- Can you... Yes.
With sesame oil?
(By the 3rd day, the 2nd oldest can read Jung Ah's mind.)
No. Please stir-fry it with a bit of cooking oil.
Put in a little bit of cooking oil.
- This will be enough.
- Okay.
- Should I stir-fry it now?
- Yes, please.
(Putting the meat in the pot)
- Add some cooking wine...
- This will be really tasty.
to get rid of the meaty odour.
I didn't know we needed cooking wine.
(While Sun Young is cooking the meat for green onion yukgaejang...)
(Jung Ah makes wild rock seaweed pot rice.)
(Even Chef Yum has never made wild rock seaweed pot rice before.)
(She puts sesame oil and chopped wild rock seaweed in the pot.)
(And she stir-fries the seaweed for a nutty flavour.)
(Next, she adds soaked rice.)
I'm worried. This is my first time making pot rice.
I'm nervous.
- Are you nervous?
- Yes.
I might burn the rice...
since I've never done this before.
(It may look simple and easy,)
(but controlling the water and heat is very tricky.)
(Worried)
- I'll wrap it up.
- Okay.
(She mixes everything well so that they'll be cooked evenly.)
Water.
(Worried Jung Ah is a bit flustered because she's anxious.)
(The water-to-rice ratio is crucial.)
(The water should just barely cover the rice.)
- What's that, Jung Ah?
- It's soy sauce for soup.
Oh, I see.
(She adds anchovy sauce for umami.)
(All that's left is to let it simmer.)
(Will the wild rock seaweed pot rice turn out okay?)
The meat is almost fully cooked.
All right. Then...
(Chef Yum's Cooking Tip)
(An easy guide to green onion yukgaejang)
Adding green onion... I should add some more.
- It's green onion yukgaejang, yes?
- Yes. Add some more.
Okay.
- Stir it well.
- Got it.
- Let's do it together.
- Oh, garlic.
You like garlic, don't you?
That's a lot of garlic. I didn't know we needed this much.
We need a lot of chilli powder.
- Stir it.
- Okay.
Stir-fry everything to infuse the chilli oil.
After that, we'll add water.
- In goes the water.
- All right.
(Once the green onion chilli oil is infused...)
(Pouring in the water)
Now, we'll let it simmer for a bit.
Just like this?
(It already looks quite tasty.)
(The youngest came to see green onion yukgaejang.)
(Gasping)
Jung Ah, it looks so good.
Does it? I haven't adjusted the saltiness yet.
(Sniffing)
My, it smells so good.
Oh, my. It looks exactly the same.
- Same as what?
- Same as the ones from restaurants.
I really like it.
It looks just like the one from the place I always order from.
(It looks good enough to sell.)
- What's that, Jung Ah?
- I'm adding a bit of anchovy sauce.
For umami.
(The anchovy sauce will boost the umami.)
- Should we add the mushroom now?
- Let's put it all in.
(Add mung bean sprouts, the essential ingredient.)
- It's already a bit spicy.
- It's already spicy.
Adding Cheongyang chilli pepper will be so tasty.
(Isn't it easy to make green onion yukgaejang?)
(Green onion yukgaejang made simple is now ready.)
(All that's left is to wait for the wild rock seaweed pot rice.)
(Fidgety)
I'm curious about this. Will the rice turn out okay?
- Is it going well?
- I don't know.
(She seems anxious and worried.)
Was the water not enough?
Should I...
I shouldn't peek inside too often.
(Worried Jung Ah can't do anything about it.)
(Unable to contain her curiosity, she opens the lid.)
I'm so curious.
(Anxiously,)
(she takes a small bite of the rice to check.)
What do I do? It's hard.
(How does it taste, Jung Ah?)
The rice is still hard.
- We can just let it simmer on low.
- Let it simmer for longer...
Right. Let it simmer on low for a long time.
It's rather a relief. Right?
(Jung Ah takes their advice...)
(and decides to let it simmer longer using the residual heat.)
(Yoon Seo has nothing to do until the rice is ready.)
(She notices the messy pile of shoes.)
(How Art Major Yoon Seo Organises Shoes)
(1. Place the shoes facing forward for easy access.)
(2. Place the boots in the corner to keep the entryway clear.)
(She lines up the slippers neatly as well.)
(The entrance is now neatly organised.)
(The second oldest notices it right away.)
Who organised the shoes?
- I did that just now.
- My, you're so sweet.
I guess Yoon Seo always...
- watches everything carefully.
- She has a sharp eye for detail.
- She's amazing.
- She majored in art.
I think it's because she majored in art.
Of course. Absolutely.
It bothers her.
Do you think it's an art major thing too?
I feel rewarded.
I guess I majored in art for this.
(She majored in art in college just for the compliments.)
(The rice should be fully cooked by now.)
I can't wait to see how the rice turned out.
(She opens the lid right away.)
(Is the wild rock seaweed pot rice cooked properly?)
(It looks good enough.)
Oh, my.
- I'll stir it.
- It looks fine.
Oh, my.
(She stirs the rice to see if it's cooked through to the bottom.)
(The wild rock seaweed pot rice is cooked through to the bottom.)
(Shiny)
The aroma is so savoury.
- Right?
- Yes.
- Is it cooked properly?
- It smells so good.
(As the wild rock seaweed pot rice turned out fluffy and moist...)
I love the savoury aroma. The seaweed smells so good.
(Let's set the table...)
(now that the wild rock seaweed pot rice is ready.)
- It's better with a lot of seaweed.
- Seaweed. Yes.
The seaweed needs to stand out. Here we go.
(She scoops the wild rock seaweed pot rice,)
(making sure that the precious wild rock seaweed stands out.)
It looks so tasty.
(The green onion yukgaejang looks even tastier now.)
- This looks really good.
- Indeed.
(Plenty of ingredients including beef, green onion,)
(mushroom, bracken, and mung bean sprouts)
(And she also scoops plenty of spicy broth.)
- Sun Young, - Yes?
can you wipe down the outside of the bowls...
- using paper towel?
- Sure. Got it.
(Groaning)
- My, it looks so delicious.
- Right?
(Her mouth is already watering.)
(But...)
Jung Ah, should I wipe the inside or the outside of the bowl?
The rims of the bowls.
Should I wipe the inside or the outside of the bowl?
(Chuckling)
Wipe away the splatters on the rim.
- You mean, the inside?
- No, the outside.
- I'll do it, Sun Young.
- No, it's... Exactly.
(Why should I clean this?)
Just for a better presentation.
Oh, like this? The splatters here?
Yes.
This is something I'll never do again.
I bet I will never do this again in my whole life.
But I should do this for the viewers, Yoon Seo.
I've never seen anyone who loved viewers that much.
I love the viewers so much.
(Viewers, let us show you their breakfast.)
I'm excited.
(Wild rock seaweed pot rice made with the seaweed they earned)
It looks good.
(Spicy green onion yukgaejang)
It smells so good.
(Seasoned squid and radish and cabbage kimchi...)
(made the previous day)
(A hearty breakfast that will keep them full)
(The two guys arrived at the perfect time.)
Good morning.
- Breakfast is served on the table.
- Good morning.
(The table is set so that they can start eating right away.)
Where are they? Guys.
Breakfast is...
- How was it?
- Sorry?
- We just went on a boat ride.
Did you have fun?
It felt good to be on the boat having You Seok driving it.
He took us to the fishing spot and back.
- As if my son gave me a tour.
- Right.
- You're back. Let's eat.
- Oh, my. This is...
- I'm amazed. This is...
- Everything looks so tasty.
- Let's dig in.
- Oh, my. It looks so good.
- You made the soup this morning.
- Yes.
(Breakfast of green onion yukgaejang and wild rock seaweed pot rice)
(Yoon Seo tries the wild rock seaweed pot rice first.)
(Amazed)
Is it good?
Oh, it's rice with seaweed.
(Her eyes pop open.)
It's good.
The pot rice is so good. Jung Ah, you pulled it off.
(The frown of the truth)
(You Seok tries the wild rock seaweed pot rice too.)
(Surprised and amazed)
My goodness.
This wild rock seaweed pot rice is so good.
It's good.
- The wild rock seaweed is tasty.
- It's tasty.
(Right?)
(The wild rock seaweed adds a nice crunch and a chewy texture.)
Oh, it's rice with seaweed.
(Crunchy, chewy)
- It's so good.
- It's good, right?
- Extra seaweed would've been nice.
- Yes.
- It's not fishy at all.
- It's not fishy. It's savoury.
It's so good.
- It's good just as I thought.
- The seaweed we harvested.
It's really precious.
(The wild rock seaweed they harvested by themselves...)
(makes the wild rock seaweed pot rice taste even better.)
Jung Ah, the pot rice is really amazing.
- Letting it steam made it perfect.
- Did you just let it steam...
- using only the residual heat?
- Yes.
- You did a wonderful job.
- Indeed.
(Try wrapping some rice in dried laver.)
(It tastes even better that way!)
(Yoon Seo tries Jung Ah's simple green onion yukgaejang too.)
- The yukgaejang is so good.
- Is it good?
It's good.
(You Seok slurps down a spoonful of the green onion yukgaejang too.)
- It's perfectly spicy.
- The yukgaejang is so good.
- It's good, isn't it?
- Seriously.
(They have a spoonful of the broth at the same time.)
(The spicy green onion chilli oil...)
(gives the green onion yukgaejang a deep, fiery flavour.)
(This spicy green onion yukgaejang...)
(goes perfectly with the savoury wild rock seaweed pot rice.)
(One more bite of the broth)
(Sighing in satisfaction)
(Jung Ah takes a big bite of bracken and mung bean sprouts.)
(They're perfectly tender, having absorbed the broth.)
(Sun Young slurps down some bracken too.)
(Exclaiming in awe)
(She takes a bite of the combination of the pot rice and yukgaejang.)
(It's so tasty.)
(Hae Joon is also more of a toppings guy than a broth guy.)
(Munching)
(This is really something.)
It's good.
(The various textures of the toppings...)
(make him fall in love with the green onion yukgaejang.)
(I'm glad I made green onion yukgaejang.)
I usually eat more side dishes than rice.
- I see.
- But I can't stop eating the rice.
(The perfect combination of savoury wild rock seaweed pot rice...)
(and spicy green onion yukgaejang...)
(makes it hard to stop eating, even though it's breakfast.)
My, it's tasty.
(The food that Jung Ah made with so much love and effort...)
(provides a hearty breakfast that keeps everyone full.)
What's the plan for the curry contest?
- She named it "curry showdown." - What time does it start?
- "Curry showdown?" - It will be held in a bit.
(The curry showdown that will take place shortly)
(The members talked about it while working the previous day.)
(The Siblings' curry showdown)
(Yum Jung Ah, the judge)
(And the four contestants)
(With the curry showdown ahead,)
(the contestants have a lot on their minds.)
- You adjusted the saltiness, right?
- Yes.
(Hae Joon takes this opportunity to get a feel for Jung Ah's palate.)
We need to remember this exact level of saltiness.
- This is how she likes her food.
- To figure out my preference?
(You need to find out her baseline for saltiness.)
So we need to make our curry based on that.
- He's very competitive.
- Yes.
(Jung Ah seems astonished by his competitiveness.)
(The other contestants start keeping him in check.)
(It won't be easy, Father.)
We'll begin the curry showdown.
I'm nervous.
(The 1st Siblings' Curry Showdown)
My usual recipe for curry is amazing.
My recipe is not that plain.
(They're out to win over the palate of Jung Ah, the judge.)
I watched many videos on YouTube.
I can make curry with my eyes closed.
So this is what it's like to be on a competition show.
(Who will be the winner of the cooking contest?)
Guys, they want us...
- to sit on the wooden bench.
- Sorry?
- We should sit on the wooden bench.
- Are we having a crisis meeting?
Go ahead.
We'll begin the curry showdown shortly.
- Yes.
You see, Tongyeong and Geoje...
- produce a lot of great crops.
- I see.
(Various crops are grown...)
(in the fertile soil of Tongyeong and Geoje.)
So we thought it'd be meaningful...
to use those high-quality local ingredients...
for your curry.
You're going to draw...
the ingredients you'll use.
- Okay.
- I see. Understood.
(I think it's a great idea.)
Everyone except for Jung Ah...
- will draw their ingredients...
- They will draw their ingredients.
- and use them to make their curry.
- I see.
Shall we begin now?
(Excited)
Hae Joon, you go first.
Just pick 1, not 2.
(She keeps him in check.)
(Looking at the others nervously)
(Choosing carefully)
- Okay.
- Let's reveal our ingredients.
- One, two, three.
- Two, three.
Onion.
(Yoon Seo: Onion)
Potato. What? I think she got a bad one.
- Onion.
- What?
(Onion, potato)
(What does "3 onions and 1 potato" mean?)
The ingredients you picked are home grown crops,
prepared for us by the local residents.
- Really?
- So that's why...
- there were only two crops.
- It must be really delicious.
You can go to the village hall to receive the ingredients...
and thank the local residents who prepared the crops.
- I see.
- Right now?
- Yes.
- Got it.
- Okay.
We should dress up nicely since we'll meet the locals.
- Should we sing a song for them?
- No, we...
Should we sing as we enter the village hall?
- You just have to bring the crops.
- Yes.
- Greet and thank them politely.
- We'll bow to them.
(Polite)
- Of course, we'll do that.
- We'll wish them a happy new year.
By the way, are we going there empty-handed?
Oh, right. We're going there empty-handed.
Shouldn't we give them something in return?
- Shall we give them the curry?
- Oh, the curry?
(Taken aback)
- I hope it's good enough to eat.
- Right.
- I hope it's delicious.
- I hope it's good enough to eat.
What if it's not good?
- We'll give them some if it's okay.
- But is curry enough for a gift?
And if not...
(Worried)
I'm worried.
(With You Seok being the last one, everyone finished getting dressed.)
- Let's get going.
- Go on.
- See you later.
- Jung Ah, we'll be back shortly.
- I'll leave this here.
Yoon Seo, you look like the Little Match Girl.
Why is your shirt buttoned up in the back?
Oh, this? It has buttons in the back.
(Yoon Seo is wearing a unique shirt that has buttons in the back.)
- Oh, this shirt is...
- It's unique.
Please give me some onions.
Young man, where are you headed?
- Come this way.
- The village hall.
Are you heading to the village hall?
- Yes.
- What was its name? Haru?
- Haru?
I heard its name. Is it Haneul?
(Gureum, 4 years old)
- This young man said...
- Ninety-two.
- he wasn't married.
Oh, my. We're here. This is the village hall.
(They arrived at the village hall where the local residents are.)
- This is it, right? The entrance...
- My goodness.
- It says "potato." Gosh.
- "Potato?"
(Screaming)
What's going on?
- It says "potato." Gosh.
- What?
- Oh, no.
- What's going on?
I'm wearing slippers.
- It says "potato." Gosh.
- What?
- Oh, no.
- What's going on?
- What?
- I have slippers on.
- What is that?
Weren't we going to the village hall?
(What happened to the onion and potato expedition?)
- Potatoes.
- Potatoes?
What's going on?
(2 cars appear in front of the onion and potato expedition.)
- What?
- I have slippers on.
(On each car is...)
(Potato)
(Onion)
- What's that?
- Weren't we going to...
the village hall?
I have slippers on, okay?
I'm digging out potatoes all alone.
What's going on here?
What? Weren't we going to the village hall?
Wasn't this the village hall?
Get in.
Isn't this the village hall?
Are we getting in?
I'm all alone.
Wait. You told us to dress up.
I'm wearing jeans.
Get in, onion and potato.
I'm not fine.
(Crying out at the unbelievable reality)
- Let me put on some sunscreen.
- I get all shy when I'm alone.
Did we do something wrong?
Why do you keep...
tricking us?
(At the verge of crying)
Jung Ah!
- Jung Ah!
(The youngsters cry out to Jung Ah.)
Save us, Jung Ah!
(But the eldest wouldn't know about it.)
I don't want to go alone.
You'll be fine, right?
(Worried)
I hate going alone the most.
(You Seok gets in the potato car alone.)
Let's turn all the cameras around.
For real.
Calm down. Once we get to the onion field,
there will be elders there.
Greet them, and then bring the onions back in our baskets.
My gut is telling me we have to dig up the onions.
No way.
(Sun Young is anxious about the sudden potential work.)
(You Seok puts on sunscreen, expecting work.)
(Rubbing it in)
This is just hilarious now.
(Laughing)
(Unusual behaviour from extreme anxiety)
This reminds me of the boat.
(Applying)
Okay, I've got it now.
I've got the hang of Fresh off the Sea now.
(Gotten the hang of Fresh off the Sea)
It's...
Really.
(At a loss for words)
Just when I put my guard down,
there's a surprise event.
(Sighing)
Tell us where we're going at the least.
We're heading to dig up onions. The onions are...
Are we going to dig them up or simply get them?
We could go to a supermarket.
- Dig them up.
Am I going alone to dig up potatoes?
(Onion, Potato)
(The two cars part ways to different destinations.)
How long will it take?
It'll take over 30 minutes.
Thirty minutes for real?
(The onion expedition heads to Geoje Island.)
I always bring my bag with me.
But I didn't bring one this time because they said...
- we'd be going to the village hall.
- I won't believe anyone now.
I'll only doubt things more.
(They were caught completely off guard again.)
Right. I let my guard down.
(Laughing)
We've got kidnapped again.
I have nothing to say.
After all, I didn't ride a boat.
- You... True.
- Right?
This annoys me the most. The onion sign.
This sign that's put up sloppy...
It's fluttering in the wind.
(Dumbfounded)
I'm taking a photo of it.
(Onion)
(Fluttering)
"Onion."
(A design that looks like they didn't even bother with it)
How annoying.
(Laughing)
(Acting strangely)
Does Jung Ah know about what's going on?
She'll find out later.
So she has no idea yet?
(Shocked)
How will she find out later?
I get it now.
Once we return from work,
Jung Ah will have cooked the curry.
Isn't that your wish, Hae Joon?
It's not a wish...
but how things roll.
(It will fade away someday)
(Acting strangely again)
You Seok is off alone to dig up potatoes.
(Curious about how the Potato Guy is doing)
He must be complaining nonstop, right?
You Seok, all alone.
You Seok lost...
- when it was 3 to 1.
- Potatoes.
He had the worst luck in the draw this time.
(Feeling bad)
Someone is calling me.
It's a video call.
(A video call from the Potato Guy)
You Seok.
- Look, Jung Ah.
- Jung Ah!
They're being kidnapped.
- Why are you there, You Seok?
- Why are you there?
(Laughing)
- Why are you there, You Seok?
- What?
What's going on?
(You Seok smiling all brightly)
(He's with Jung Ah?)
(Everyone is totally puzzled.)
Wait, why is he there? The potatoes...
What's this? What about the potatoes?
- Potatoes...
- I already dug up the potatoes.
You dug up the potatoes?
I did. I already dug up potatoes.
(You Seok already dug up the potatoes?)
Really.
(10 minutes ago in the potato car)
Why are you doing this to me?
Why did I draw the potato?
Hae Joon should've drawn the potato.
(You Seok leaves alone in the potato car.)
(Laughing)
(Glancing)
What?
(Looking around)
(The potato car returns to the Siblings' House.)
What's going on?
Good work. You can get out now.
(What?)
What?
(You Seok gathers his belongings in a rush.)
(Getting off fast)
(Surprised)
(Laughing)
(You Seok comes running with something in the basket.)
I'm saved.
(Inside You Seok's basket)
Jung Ah!
(Potatoes)
Jung Ah.
(You Seok gets a free pass from working!)
Where is Jung Ah?
Jung Ah, come out for a bit. This is bad.
(He must let Jung Ah know about this news!)
Jung Ah.
(Opening)
She was in the bathroom.
- What?
- I called you.
What for?
Sit for a minute. I have a funny story to tell.
Seriously, I...
We were heading down, playing pretend and stuff.
They said the village hall was down there, and we got there.
But suddenly, two cars drove in.
One potato car. One onion car.
Did they get kidnapped?
I was kidnapped, and so was the onion team.
I was alone in the car.
"I can't do it alone. There won't be enough airtime."
"It's hard for me." I kept grumbling.
But after a drive around the neighbourhood,
I was told to get off with the potatoes. I was saved.
- And...
- Have the guys been kidnapped?
They went to dig up onions.
Mine were bought. I was all alone.
I kept saying I couldn't go alone.
"I can't go." I kept saying that.
(How did you get here?)
I was saved all alone.
I can't believe you right now.
No, believe me.
I even called you...
after getting kidnapped. I video-called you.
- What is it, Jung Ah?
- Lock the door!
Where are you going, Jung Ah?
- You're being strange right now.
- Listen.
- You're too hyper.
- I...
It's because I was kidnapped earlier.
- No.
- Jung Ah, I...
- Jung Ah.
- I can't believe you.
Come over here, Jung Ah.
I wouldn't kidnap you, would I?
Come, Jung Ah.
Let's try calling Yoon Seo.
I have to cook.
Seriously, Jung Ah.
Why can't you believe me?
- Of course, I can't.
- How come?
Why not?
- Whatever.
- I'll prove it to you.
Call Yoon Seo.
(A deep mistrust sparked by the wasabi incident)
Let's call Yoon Seo as she's getting kidnapped.
(Feeling wronged)
If only it weren't for that wasabi incident.
- What...
- We're going to...
Geoje Island right now!
- What?
- We're going to Geoje Island!
The potato was the good one.
Gosh, this is really...
What a series of twists.
Fresh off the Sea is no joke.
This isn't the kind of Fresh off the Sea I knew.
Let's video call at the onion field.
I'll call while digging up onions.
(After the call with the Potato Guy)
(In despair)
Good. I'm rather happy.
Earlier, I was like,
"What's going on?"
"Why draw papers when there are five of us?"
I had my questions.
- The production staff was thorough.
- Yes.
Imagine how excited they must have been.
(Spaced out)
If I knew the car ride would be this long...
Just imagine how ridiculous we must have been to them.
- Like, "They don't know a thing." - We must've been funny to them.
Don't film us!
(Production staff)
- What?
- Don't film us!
(Onion)
(Don't film us!)
(How could we not?)
(Haranguing)
(Laughing)
What?
(Breathing out heavily)
The production staff is filming us with a phone while smiling!
They look happy...
when we look all stressed out.
(Fluttering)
What chaos.
Should we take it off?
Yes.
(Taking it down immediately)
As expected of an art major. Nice.
- You're...
- How...
quick to act.
(Meanwhile at the Siblings' House)
- You believe me now, right?
- No.
I'll try to calm down.
Earlier, I was excited.
- Were you?
- The happiness that I was saved.
I went back and forth from paradise to the pit.
- I see.
- So open the door for me.
No, stay in your room.
- I'll stay here.
- Let's talk in the living room.
Shouldn't we talk in the living room...
- and secure airtime?
- You.
You're trying to kidnap me, aren't you?
I'll just...
(Screaming)
(Scared to death)
You should trust me, Jung Ah. Aren't we a family?
Why are you trying so hard to be with me?
- Just why?
- Being alone is lonely.
Let's hang out together. Come.
He's being weird.
(She still can't trust him.)
Please open the door, Jung Ah.
Why do you want to be with me?
Go and sleep in your room.
Jung Ah, we...
- Can I really just sleep?
- Yes.
Can I?
Go to your room. I have to cook.
- I'm going to my room.
- Okay.
(Giving up)
- I'm going to sleep.
- Okay.
(Closing)
(After hearing You Seok's room door close)
(Glancing)
(Window)
(Sealed shut)
Let's lock it.
(After locking the window)
(Opening)
(Carefully scanning the living room)
(After checking that You Seok's room door is shut)
(Quickly heading to the kitchen)
(Appearing)
(You Seok was watching the whole thing.)
(Jung Ah has no idea about it.)
(He's off to meet her now.)
Jung Ah.
You scared me.
(Dopamine level at its max)
Jung Ah.
What is it?
- I swear it's nothing.
- Right?
Either way, I need to cook.
Let's talk for a bit.
Why do you want to talk?
(Let's hear you out for now.)
You can't suddenly drag me somewhere or anything.
This isn't...
You said Fresh off the Sea wasn't like that.
No, but it changed.
(Feeling uneasy)
We went down the street, all excited.
(You Seok finally goes on a passionate rant.)
(Done briefing)
(Holding his breath)
The thing about the village hall elders was a lie,
- wasn't it?
- Yes.
They did head to the village hall.
Do you mean the village hall on Geoje Island?
(Laughing)
We never lied, you know?
You meant the village hall on Geoje Island?
Will they be receiving some onions,
not digging them up?
(Are they simply receiving some onions from the village hall?)
Is it to our left?
- Wherever it is, there must be...
- We must be here.
onions that need harvesting.
(Arrived)
Thank you, sir.
See you later, sir.
We're here.
- The elders are here.
- This town's village hall.
Right here.
(Songjin Village Village Hall, Senior Citizen Center)
(A village hall on Geoje Island)
(Onion greets the siblings.)
- This is where we get the onions.
- We get the onions here.
- Really? Not the field?
- From the elders.
- The village hall is right here.
- Are we not going to the field?
- We're not.
- What a bummer.
Do we go in together?
- Hi.
- Welcome.
Hi.
(Geoje Island, Jangmok-myeon)
(10 minutes later)
(Working clothes)
I hate you.
(No surprises.)
- Was it not...
- I feel betrayed.
Don't film us. Don't, okay?
Such a move is...
- Fresh off the Sea...
- She's walking to the camera.
- Don't film us.
- Please wait.
Don't film us.
Stop.
Directors have the cameras.
Why is a producer filming with a phone?
Don't film us.
(Laughing)
First, warm up.
(Hae Joon warms up immediately.)
And then dig up onions.
If you're all warmed up...
What?
Where is it? Where do we go?
That way, and then this way.
Let's go, guys!
- Let's go.
- I'm going for...
(What's waiting for the onion expedition?)
a bedwetter style.
- Good.
- You get it, right?
Really, this place is amazing.
(This place boasts a lush, green view.)
(Songjin Village on the pristine coast of Geoje)
(Known as the Onion Village)
Thirty to forty percent is onions.
(Most of the village is onion fields.)
(Grown in the sea breeze blowing in from the nearby ocean)
These onions are sweeter and less pungent...
than other onions because they grow...
in the sea breeze.
(It's sweet even when eaten raw.)
(The onions are nice and plump.)
Please eat plenty and stay healthy.
(Geoje onion)
(Songjin Village, filled with onions everywhere)
This road is cute.
(Planning to work hard)
- Those are all onions.
- I thought they were green onions.
No, they're onions.
- Is this how they grow?
- Yes.
Green onions... So these are onions.
They look identical to green onions.
(At first glance, the onions look like wilted green onions.)
(But the onion stalks originally stand upright.)
(As nutrients gather in the onion bulb,)
(the stalks begin to fall over.)
(I got all the nutrients!)
(Just like rice bows its head as it ripens,)
(onions do the same.)
- Hi.
Where you are right now is...
- Songjinpo, the Onion Village.
- I see.
Carefully harvest the onions you need...
for the curry showdown.
(But to make the curry...)
Two onions?
- Are we getting paid?
But...
Our pay...
We'd like to know the reward we get before getting started.
We have to set it in stone right now.
Or they could change their words.
We'll tell you how much you have to harvest...
after you learn how to dig up the onions.
- Let's get to work.
- Okay.
We're in your care.
Likewise.
Let's start from here.
- Here?
- Yes.
Okay.
Pull one out at a time.
- One?
- Yes.
There's no need to rush. Take your time.
- Take our time?
(Peel back the plastic covering.)
(Gently dig away the soil around the roots.)
(Lift it carefully without damaging the stalks or roots.)
(Focused and fascinated)
If the onion neck snaps off, it loses its market value.
The onion neck?
As you pull the onion out, you'll realise...
- how fragile the neck is.
- Right.
There are times when the neck will snap off.
It'll be bad if you damage the product.
- Don't damage the product.
- No.
- Got it.
- Damage...
- Give it a shot.
- Okay.
Even if you're only harvesting one,
- do it properly.
- Slowly?
You need to cut it later.
Cut what?
Cut it while leaving about 1cm of the neck intact.
Only then will the product still have its value.
I see.
(It can be shipped directly without any damage!)
- Got it?
- Yes.
Leave about this much.
Each net has to be filled with 20kg of onions.
(Gather the onions with the necks cut off.)
(Put them in an onion net.)
No other onions are as good as Geoje Island onions.
- Is that so?
- Geoje Island onions?
So they're the best.
- Give it a try.
- Okay.
- We'll start harvesting.
- Good.
Got it. Harvest nonstop.
- From now on.
- Nonstop.
Slowly.
Right.
- Shall we start?
- Use your fingers.
(Hoe at the ready.)
- Tear the plastic off ruthlessly.
- Tear it off ruthlessly.
Okay.
(Pulling out the onion)
(Pulling out the onions is fun.)
Like this.
(Even the youngest, Yoon Seo)
Just pull it out.
- Okay.
- Don't damage it.
Okay, I'll be careful.
Be gentle.
(Being careful so as not to damage the onions)
Like so.
I think using my hands is better.
(Meanwhile, Sun Young is...)
Like this.
Like this. See?
The hoe is a hassle to me.
I know I won't break the neck.
Gently like so.
Wiggle it a little, and done.
Okay. Nice.
Like this.
All good, right? Nice.
(Working hard in their own ways)
I've never seen such huge onions.
(But harvesting onions...)
My eyes.
(can be hard on the eyes.)
(Blinking hard)
(Putting on sunglasses)
Sir, the hoe.
It's good.
(He bends down and starts working in earnest.)
(Wearing the item had a huge effect!)
Don't your eyes sting? You're wearing sunglasses.
You have an item.
Goodness.
(Yoon Seo, life is all about having the right items.)
(Onions piled up thanks to the item)
It's so big.
(Everyone is working hard.)
Do you see the onion bag in front of you?
Yes, go on.
One bag can fit 21kg of onions.
- Yes.
- We'll just fill up five bags...
and call it a day.
Five bags, so that's 105kg.
(5 bags equal 105kg maximum.)
How many onions fit in one bag?
- About 50 to 60.
About 50 to 60 onions in one bag.
That means, 5 by 50 equals 250. Okay.
- We need 250.
- We can finish it in no time.
Let's go.
I'll be fast. I'll really dig up a lot.
I got it.
Be fast.
(Wasp Sun Young mode)
- Am I going fast enough?
- You're good.
Thanks. I can do well.
I'm a countryside girl.
Okay.
I got it.
(Going berserk)
It's no joke, right?
I'm getting faster.
(I'll follow you, Sun Young.)
Two hundred fifty.
(Do not forget 250.)
(Quietly focusing on his labour to hit the goal)
This isn't much.
- Exactly. It isn't that much.
- We'll be done in no time.
Take up farming after you retire. You're good.
You can take up farming.
This is the third time someone has suggested that. Right?
(Following the sea squirt and seaweed labours,)
They're casting us.
(the onion labour adds to the consecutive casting offers.)
- We're lucky.
- Sorry?
We're lucky to meet the actors we like.
Right. You know Gwan Sik, right?
Yes, we know. We know all of you.
(Today, he's Farmer Gwan Sik.)
And you are Sun Woo's mom.
Where's that, Ssangmun-dong.
Ssangmun-dong.
You all look much prettier in person.
- Thank you.
- My gosh.
You're driving me crazy.
(Yoon Seo, who's much prettier in person as verified by the lady)
(Cheered by the compliment, they work hard again.)
(Hoe ready)
(Using her hand again)
I need to use a hoe for this.
This is a really tough one.
This is huge.
(A tough one halts Wasp Sun Young.)
(She fixes her posture.)
(The fight against the tough one starts.)
(She grabs the onion stalk like she's grabbing hair.)
Let's go.
Okay, don't pull here.
Curry...
(Gently digging up the onion stuck in the ground)
(Pull it out gently so it doesn't bruise.)
Done. It's no joke.
Okay, the big ones.
Nice. It's huge.
(She keeps pulling out big ones.)
- Gosh, it's big.
- My gosh.
Look at this.
(Hae Joon finds a big one too.)
This is an onion? Watermelon...
(It should be called a watermelon.)
This is huge.
(Struggling)
(The onion is as big as Yoon Seo's face.)
- I feel good when I find big ones.
- Me too.
Do the big ones and small ones taste the same?
The big ones taste good.
- The big ones taste good?
- Yes.
- The big ones are juicy.
- Juicy.
- And it has more sugar.
- It has more sugar.
I should buy big ones when I go grocery shopping.
This is super huge.
(It's huge, so it's tasty.)
It's huge.
This is no joke. Okay.
Nice, the big ones.
This is big.
Dear viewers.
Geoje Island's onions...
grow in the soils incomparable to others,
and they're juicy because of the sea breeze.
(Pfft)
- Okay.
- Soil gets in your mouth, right?
Yes.
Everyone should wear a mask.
(It's harder to work because the wind blows the soil.)
This soil is nothing if I can please the viewers.
Hello. I came to harvest onions.
(The rising communicator)
This is a small one.
This is how you harvest it.
Do this with the hoe.
(The rising communicator stumbles, but she still does her best.)
You can pull it out.
Bye.
(She doesn't have much to say.)
Is it your first time working on a field with so many onions?
- Yes.
- Definitely.
Do you work from 7am to 5pm?
- From 7am to 5pm?
- Yes.
(During the harvest season, they work all day.)
This is tough work.
Exactly. How do you do this? I admire you.
(Experiencing it herself makes her admire them.)
How can you do this work for so long?
That's so big.
(Meanwhile, Hae Joon digs up onions silently.)
(Grunting)
(The only sounds he makes are his grunts.)
(Sighing)
- Gosh, my back.
- Your back hurts, right?
Goodness.
Let's go.
(Tall Hae Joon has to bend more, so it's hard for him.)
(Nevertheless, he has to do it.)
- You can't be silent, Hae Joon.
- What?
- You can't only work. Speak.
- Work?
Tell us an onion-related story.
(He's a fool who has his eyes only on onions.)
This job is unexpectedly tough.
(They've been crouching to work for 50 minutes.)
My back.
(The crouching position makes her back ache.)
(They're getting exhausted.)
Dear viewers.
I'm so exhausted.
(The communication king even relays the news of her being exhausted.)
This is very tough.
(The exhaustion reminds them of a song.)
(Yangpa sings "Love.. What is it")
(Please tell me I've heard wrong)
(Onion, what are you to make me cry)
(Why do you drive me crazy)
(I hate myself more)
(For still loving you)
(Onions, I love you.)
Didn't we dig up around 100?
- One hundred?
- Yes.
- Really?
- Did we not?
(Still a long way to go until the target amount)
I'll make sure we dig up 250.
When will we harvest 250? Can we do it in no time?
We didn't know how important the lots were.
(Suddenly feeling wronged)
You Seok is resting at home because he got lucky...
with the draw?
What are You Seok and Jung Ah doing?
Make You Seok do some hard labour too!
How is this possible? This labour is no joke!
(While Sun Young gradually gets angrier,)
(back at home...)
I'm bored.
(She's leisurely taking care of herself with the music.)
(Shaking)
It's boring without the rest.
(Her dance betrays her words.)
(Where is You Seok?)
(You Seok is reading a book.)
(He looks like he's enjoying the gap between classes.)
(Senior Kang, acting major)
(Senior Kang is focused on his book.)
(Senior Kang reads the same page of the same book every day.)
(Still on the same page)
(Blinking)
(But his eyes look very bored.)
(He loses his focus in less than a page.)
(Distracted)
(Sunken eyes)
(He's just bored.)
You Seok, did we finish the snacks yesterday?
(Senior Kang closes his book as soon as Jung Ah calls.)
We finished them, right?
Seriously.
(Chewing)
I don't know if I should be doing this.
- I feel bad.
- I feel so bad for feeling bored.
(Enjoying the free time with the snack)
Let us take pictures.
The others must be sweating and working hard.
(They do them.)
(We'll leave memories.)
One, two, three.
(A sweet photo of them)
We do everything, from riding a boat to working on a farm.
- Seriously.
- Yes. You've been through a lot.
We're almost done.
(They're almost done with harvesting onions.)
I'm good at this.
(Everyone becomes an expert in onion harvest.)
(She sacrifices her knees.)
There you go.
(Working hard until the end)
(They don't stop until they hit the 250 mark.)
(Surrounded by onions)
- I think we're done.
- Really?
We have enough.
This is enough.
One can cut off the stalks, and one can bag the onions.
Do I cut off this much?
(How do you cut off onion stalks?)
- You can hold the leaf.
- Yes.
This much.
As it dries, it shrinks.
So leave quite a bit.
- Leave a bit?
- About two centimetres?
Okay.
(With scissors)
(He starts cutting onion stalks.)
(Humming)
(He still doesn't talk, but he pumps himself up by humming.)
The scissors are convenient.
This is nothing compared to digging them up.
I love onions.
I add onions to almost all the food.
(A cutting machine with nonstop communication activates.)
(The art student's bold cuts)
I think I'm good.
I'll be fast.
You should do it right even if it slows you down.
(Very meticulous)
He's become like the owner.
(Owner Hae Joon cuts the onion stalks properly.)
(He gathers the stalk-less onions.)
- Put them inside.
- Pardon?
- Into the bag.
- Into the bag?
(Time to put them into the bag)
I can't just pour them in, can I?
- Just pour them.
- I can?
(Embarrassed)
(My precious onions)
(Rolling into the bag)
(The bag is more than half full.)
It's heavy.
(Yoon Seo has it completely filled.)
- Pour them out.
- Pour them out?
Yes.
(Rolling down)
Done.
(They've already filled up almost 2 full bags of onions.)
I'll work hard.
Please give me a lot of wage.
(The onions Sun Young cut while chattering)
Let's go.
(Hae Joon lifts them up.)
(He's good at pouring them out now.)
(3 bags full already)
- Now...
- We're done.
(Feeling proud)
You need to add more.
- You need to add more.
- Fill it up completely?
Completely.
(This isn't easy.)
- You can put that in too.
- This is good, right?
Look at this.
- Put that in as well.
- My goodness.
(Another big one)
(He keeps adding the onions.)
It's completely full.
My gosh.
Put in a few more.
- Three or four.
- More?
One more.
- One more.
- One more?
(How many more are you adding?)
You need to fill it up completely.
(Even when you fill it up until it spills over,)
(it doesn't break.)
(1 completely-filled up bag)
It's done. Try carrying it.
(Surprised)
(Struggling)
Gosh, this...
(Heavy)
- Let's carry it.
- To that side?
This is heavy.
(An unexpected workout with the 20kg load)
My gosh.
(4 more bags to go)
(He delivers 1 more bag right away.)
Here they are. Which bag do I fill up?
(Down to one last precious onion)
We got a really big one.
(They keep filling up the bags.)
We're done.
(The 3rd bag)
- The onions are heavy.
- How did he carry it by himself?
I'm glad I did something on the show.
I agree.
Was it 20kg?
It's 20kg.
(They harvested 100kg in total.)
(And the present from the onion farm)
- You worked hard.
- Thanks.
Here.
Next.
- Thank you.
- Thank you, sir.
Thank you.
(The onions of Songjinpo, Geoje, harvested by the onion expedition,)
(were delivered to the customers...)
(around the nation.)
- Thank you. Bye.
- Good job.
- Bye.
- Thank you.
- Good job.
- Thanks for the onions.
- Stay healthy.
- You guys are amazing, really.
- Hae Joon, aren't you exhausted?
- It's okay.
Goodness.
We can't be worn out just from working this much...
- when they work all day.
- Exactly.
What we did was nothing.
(They appreciate the value of labour once again.)
Seriously.
(Grunting)
Gosh, my back.
(The onion expedition gets ready to go home with grunts.)
I'm beat.
(His hair is a mess.)
(The aftertaste of the labour leaves him dishevelled.)
(His neat self before the work is nowhere to be found.)
You don't know when you'll be taken away to work,
so I'll prepare all my clothes to be suitable for labour.
(Tattered)
(He still can't believe he was dragged to an onion farm.)
(After a long struggle, they head home with the onions...)
(for the curry showdown.)
(The front row passengers fall asleep from the hard labour.)
(But he's wide awake.)
(Rolling his eyes)
They've all fallen asleep.
Sorry?
I... Nothing.
She's not sleeping.
If they're sleeping...
Is he talking to himself?
I like being quiet.
I enjoy the times...
where you can understand each other...
without talking.
(Hae Joon starts a monologue.)
It must've weighed on his mind that he was quiet during work.
You didn't say anything...
when you were working.
When I was working on the onions,
I talked too little.
You talked way too little.
- I tried to get you to talk, - And...
but your answers...
- I want to continue...
- He's very funny.
to talk to myself.
I refuse to have a conversation.
He refuses to have a conversation and will talk to himself.
Why do you refuse to have a conversation?
(She finds him very funny.)
(Don't talk to me. I'll talk to myself.)
I...
When I dug up onions,
there was dust on my mouth,
and I felt thirsty.
I wanted to peel the onion and chew it.
I...
The big onion...
is very juicy, apparently.
I could've asked for water,
- Why didn't you?
- but my pride didn't allow it.
Why does that hurt your pride?
- For something so trivial...
- Trivial.
My thirst...
(His pride didn't allow him to feel thirsty.)
Is this a monologue or a conversation?
- I'm getting confused, but...
- But.
after today's filming ends,
you know the house?
In the house,
- I plan to do that.
- "That."
- Curry?
- It's...
"Not Fresh off the Sea."
How does it sound?
You'll steal the show?
- You'll take over?
- I don't like the title.
- You don't like the title.
- So...
I'll change Fresh off the Sea...
- to "Not Fresh off the Sea." - "Not Fresh off the Sea."
Look forward to "Not Fresh off the Sea."
(They return home with Hae Joon's never-ending monologue.)
Let's carry the onions
(The onion expedition is back home.)
Gosh, Hae Joon.
(Father.)
Take this.
Give me that.
It's heavy. Be careful.
(The onions are heavier because they're bigger and fuller.)
(Jung Ah goes to welcome the others.)
- You'll dirty your clothes.
- It's okay.
- Go on.
- Go, it's heavy.
- Let's go.
- Hurry up.
(They all head back to the Siblings' House.)
There are onions here!
- What? We have onions.
- There are onions here.
There are onions. Darn it.
They were right in front of the house.
We could've just pulled them out using bare hands.
My gosh.
But they're not comparable.
You can't compare them. When you pulled out the stalk...
- The stalk was so much thicker.
- That's some crazy onion.
- Isn't it huge?
- It's crazy.
The bigger it is, the juicier it is.
My gosh.
- You worked so hard.
- It's so...
(The last ingredient for the curry showdown has arrived.)
- The onions are...
- They're huge.
no joke.
Jung Ah, you can't be thinking...
that these are all we dug up, right?
Five bags.
We dug up more than five bags.
- Really?
- We just filled up five bags.
Really? You worked so hard.
(Come here, Sun Young.)
Jung Ah.
(At the sound of her cry, Yoon Seo joins.)
This is what Fresh off the Sea is about.
- You worked hard.
- This is enough.
(A bitter laugh)
We bought ice cream.
- My gosh.
- Would you like one?
- Yes.
- I'll bring them over.
I'd like that.
(The siblings decide to take a short rest.)
(They sit around on the platform with cool ice cream.)
(Groaning)
(Washing his face powerfully)
What's wrong with him?
Here. Do this.
(Here comes a helping hand.)
(Much more comfortable)
It's cool.
My gosh.
(Washing his face)
(What a funny guy.)
Hae Joon.
(The younger members laugh at his antics.)
(Tapping his feet to prepare for the next step)
(Rubbing his foot)
I've always wanted...
to do this.
Washing feet and splashing water on my back...
by an outdoor faucet.
It was my dream.
(The dream of the cool guy)
When you use a towel,
wipe your face first, then later your feet.
Some wipe the feet before the face.
Who does that?
(Me.)
(He wiped his feet with that towel just now.)
That was nice.
It feels great after washing up.
I just need to wash the stuff you bought, right?
You Seok and I will wash the ingredients.
Get changed and get some rest.
(Ordering the three to rest as they're tired from working)
(You Seok and Jung Ah are in charge of rinsing the ingredients.)
I'll peel the potatoes. You only need to wash them.
Okay.
(Washing the ingredients clean for the curry showdown)
- Jung Ah.
- Yes?
- For the curry showdown, - Yes.
there should be more judges, not just you.
There should be judges from the production staff...
- to give scores.
- Let's do that. Okay.
You'll give 50 points...
while the other 5 will give 10 points each.
Let's decide who the winner is that way.
Jung Ah, what do you think about my idea?
I like it.
(How will this decision affect the result of the showdown?)
Jung Ah, what should I choose for my nickname?
(Sun Young can't decide on her nickname.)
Yes? Give me an idea.
Something fun like Auntie Omakase.
- How about this, Sun Young?
- What?
Auntie Curry, instead of Auntie Omakase.
- Nice. Auntie Curry.
- Auntie Curry.
Auntie Curry.
Auntie Curry, not Auntie Omakase.
Auntie Curry. I love it.
Was it Auntie?
- Auntie...
- Auntie Curry.
Auntie Curry.
(Laughing)
- Auntie Curry.
- Auntie Curry. Wait.
- No one will understand it.
I'm Auntie Curry.
(Saying the name makes them happy)
I'm so sorry, but can I fart?
- Do you want me to go out?
- No.
- Do you want me to scream?
- No, it's going...
Do you want to fart on the count of three?
- It went back inside.
- Did it?
If you can fart in front of each other, you're pretty close.
Yes.
Are they prepping the ingredients right now?
(You Seok is the one making noise.)
(He's microwaving something.)
(What is this thing You Seok prepared secretly?)
- Could you give me one too?
- Yes.
- Here.
- Thank you.
Where did it go? Where's my meat?
(Studying the recipe again for the last time)
Onions... Gosh.
I'm all set. Am I?
Gosh. This will complicate things.
Goodness.
(The tension mounts as the showdown gets closer.)
(Serious)
Let's go. It's time for war.
(Let's go. It's time for war.)
(Can anyone really make curry?)
(If I cook the way I usually cook, it'll be too good.)
(I have two secret weapons that I'll use in the end.)
(I have about 12 secret weapons.)
This is what a competition show feels like.
- We'll begin the curry war.
- Yes.
(Siblings' Showdown: Curry Class Wars)
It's my first time making curry.
Do You Know Hidden is my nickname.
It means, "Do you know about my hidden secrets?"
I'm going to use coffee powder and yuzu marmalade.
I've watched the YouTube video many times.
My goal is to finish the dish well.
He's my competition.
What is that? What's that gun?
Hello.
I'm Indian Matfia.
What's up with him?
What's wrong with him? Seriously.
What?
I'm Matfia from India.
So I can make curry with my eyes closed.
I'll make it with my eyes shut.
I'm done with my curry.
(What's Indian Matfia's secret weapon?)
Are you confident you'll win?
If I am not the winner, who will?
Me.
- I'll be the winner for sure.
- Me.
(White Spoon, Auntie Curry)
Salute!
I'll do my best today, like always.
I'm going to make 1990s-style curry...
that we had when we were young.
Mine isn't that ordinary.
- Are you confident of winning?
- Of course.
I'll show how I take first place for the viewers.
My dish is called PR for Tongyeong.
I'm Plump Ravioli With Joons.
Actually, curry is really easy to make.
So I want to challenge myself.
I'm going to add dumplings. It'll be experimental.
I think this moment...
will get the highest ratings.
"Culinary Class Wars?"
Come on.
(Curry showdown begins now.)
- I'm nervous.
- Really?
- Why?
- I'm not nervous at all.
(A judge who will evaluate these strong contenders)
She's here.
How pretty!
- Hello.
- Hi.
(Head chef of Fresh off the Sea)
- Nice to meet you.
- Yes.
- Chef Yum.
(It's an honour to meet you.)
- Okay. Are you all ready?
- Yes.
Yes, Master.
In fact, curry is a dish anyone can make.
The one who makes the curry that the general public likes...
- will likely win.
- The general public.
That's what I think.
The cooking process is really important.
Are you evaluating the process too?
That's fundamental to cooking.
I'll check if the process is hygienic.
That's going to cost me lots of points.
You can't eat with your hands while making noise.
And you can't drool into the food, can you?
Are you starting now?
Yes. We'll begin the curry showdown.
Okay.
I'll prepare the ingredients first.
(The participants prepare their ingredients.)
She said it's important to be hygienic.
That's mine.
I'm going to use it.
You have to be fast.
Gosh.
This is a war, indeed.
What was it? What do I put in?
Hold on. Salt, sugar, pepper.
The chef right here is checking the recipe now.
No, I am not.
(Chef Yum starts evaluating the participants.)
(Chopping)
(Plump Ravioli With Joons is skilfully prepping.)
Joons seems to have...
lots of experience cooking.
Yes. It's...
I said this was a challenge for myself.
I said it because...
But why are your clothes so dirty...
- when you're cooking?
- That's a point against him!
- It's...
- That's a deduction.
- It's possible.
- It's from the onion harvesting.
But...
the clothes carry the scent of Geoje Island's onions.
(Sniffing)
You do smell like onions.
I love this onion scent.
Roughly chop the onions.
Keep things clean. Am I right?
Be hygienic.
You always have to cook in a clean environment.
I'll throw away the piece that fell from the board.
Okay. Did you see that, Judge Yum?
I won't use anything that falls off the cutting board.
(Yoon Seo's wind shield)
Goodness.
I'll help you.
I'll help you with it.
I'll do it myself, Sun Young.
No, I'll do it.
Is it...
- a deduction...
- No.
- not to get help from others?
- Those who know how to be loved...
- also know how to love.
- I didn't want to burden you.
Okay.
Judge, I'm doing okay with the hygiene so far, right?
- Yes. It's totally hygienic.
- Gosh.
- Don't worry about it now.
I didn't lose points.
If I don't lose points for being dirty, I'll win it.
She's writing something.
(Deducting points for spitting from talking too much)
Good.
(Meanwhile...)
What is this? Was it pre-cooked?
I haven't cooked it yet. I just microwaved it...
to dry it out.
- I see.
- I need to caramelize it.
- And it'll take too long.
- Gosh. I'm going to do that too.
- Otherwise, it'll take too long.
- Okay.
(His strategy to reduce the caramelizing time)
(Meticulous planning skills)
(Staring)
(Shaking)
(Glancing)
Do your hands shake like that all the time?
I have shaky hands.
- Shaky hands.
- Yes.
Shaky hands.
You Seok is well-prepared.
He microwaved the onions.
I should've done that too.
To let the moisture out easily,
I was told to chop it against the grain.
- Okay. Sure.
- Yes.
(Uneven)
Have you made curry before?
This is my first time making it.
- It's your first time.
- Really?
- Yes.
- That's minus five points.
- She has never made it before?
- That's possible.
- She's young.
That's totally possible.
Get cooked quickly.
(What's the recipe...)
(for Do You Know Hidden's first curry in her life?)
Stir-fry the meat.
I'll stir-fry the onions in the oil from the meat.
I heard that would bring out the flavours.
Unlike others, I'll use cabbage.
I'll add a little bit of sugar.
That will speed up the caramelization.
They're still a little moist, but they are tasty as is.
Also, there are two kicks to the recipe.
- Are you going to kick me?
- Yes.
I'm going to kick him.
(Playing along with his joke)
(Laughing)
Get it!
Now, I'll add the curry.
(Auntie Curry is the first to add the curry blocks.)
Let's dissolve it.
I've never used this brand before.
I don't know how it'll turn out.
Actually, when I cook at home,
I don't stir-fry them in butter.
I usually use avocado oil to be healthy.
But today, I'm using butter to focus only on the taste.
There is something I have to do personally.
That's...
- What?
- an ordinary curry, isn't it?
It's the curry dads cook on Sundays.
- Mine isn't that ordinary.
- Is that so?
- Okay.
- Does it have a kick to it?
- Of course.
- Okay.
Don't worry.
- You'll add apples.
- That's right.
I always add apples.
If I put too much butter,
it can be too greasy.
It's because I'm adding cheese too.
Apples and cheese are my secrets.
(She'll make to sweet and flavourful with apples and cheese.)
Apples make it tastier.
Actually, I add water at this stage.
I don't stir-fry it for too long. I let it simmer.
Once the ingredients are cooked, I'm done.
(Is Auntie Curry's dish finished just like that?)
(In the meantime,)
(Plump Ravioli With Joons is cooking smoothly too.)
(Glancing)
(MSG)
(Adding MSG without looking, unbeknownst to Chef Yum)
(He dreams of a perfect crime.)
(Chef Yum approaches.)
(Nervous)
- Did you add meat?
- Pardon?
- Meat?
- I don't add meat.
- It doesn't include meat.
- No, it doesn't.
(Laughing out of relief)
Wait, what was I going to do?
(Staring)
I'll microwave something downstairs.
(To thaw the dumplings)
Why am I...
(Running)
(He's busy all by himself.)
(Getting ready to thaw them right away)
I'm feeling dizzy.
I'm dizzy.
(Zoning out)
A Korean melon?
A Korean melon.
(Rinsing the Korean melon as if he thought of something)
(Suddenly, it makes him curious.)
Do I need to try this hard?
Do I not need to do this?
Okay. Jumping.
(Joons finally made it back.)
Gosh. Water needs to boil.
(Another problem)
Gosh. This is exhausting.
(Returning)
(While Joons is scurrying around frantically...)
I'm done with my dish.
- Really? Are you finished?
- That's all.
A lot needs to be cooked.
- That's all I needed to do.
- What's that?
(He has a bucketful of ingredients that need to be cooked.)
- That's 90 percent of my cooking.
- That looks good.
Curry is all about effort.
(Adding the ingredients to the caramelized onions)
(After stir-frying various vegetables and meat,)
(he adds the water after measuring it meticulously.)
(Another secret ingredient from the serious curry maker)
(Dark chocolate?)
This is all done.
(The key is to bring out the flavours and umami with dark chocolate.)
Now, I'm confident that I'll win.
Here are my secret ingredients.
(It's time for Do You Know Hidden to add her secret ingredients.)
A little bit of coffee powder.
Adding the yuzu marmalade is the kick in my recipe.
Its colour will change. It's visually more pleasing too.
(Glancing)
Judge, do we lose points for leaving our stations so often?
(The one who leaves his station often)
(Panting)
Why do I have to hurry?
(Nobody told him to hurry.)
It's...
(He suddenly opens the packet of lemon juice.)
(Recharging himself with vitamin C)
Gosh. I feel a little more energized.
(Getting a refill)
(Chugging lemon juice in a hurry)
(Sighing)
(Joons is back for real this time.)
(Is he pouring the boiled water...)
(over the dumplings?)
- That wasn't it.
- He made a mistake.
He made a mistake.
- A mistake in the process.
- He made a mistake.
(To make matters worse...)
Darn it. I don't care.
I shouldn't have added that water.
(It's Joons' lucky day.)
- Do you get angry easily?
- No.
- If you get angry while cooking, - Yes.
- the food absorbs the anger.
- Right.
So I cook with a good heart.
- That looks like an unusual curry.
- You're right.
"How much will they enjoy it?"
That's what's on my mind.
(And determined Joons' secret dish)
(After thinly slicing the Korean melon,)
(he drizzles the starch syrup over it.)
(He also adds the lemon juice he had before.)
Is that a Korean melon?
This is just a side dish.
It'll refresh your palate.
(A Korean melon side dish to refresh your palate)
(Falling)
(No!)
- My goodness.
- No.
I can make it again in no time.
This is the problem. It's...
(Will Joons be able to finish his curry safely?)
Why did I...
My goodness. I'm sorry.
It's okay.
(Auntie Curry looks relaxed next to Joons.)
Are you done, Sun Young?
- I'm waiting for it to be cooked.
- Really?
Is it simmering?
Nice. Great.
I'll taste it.
(How does it taste?)
Gosh. What's wrong with this curry?
Hold on.
(Auntie Curry is at a loss for words.)
I think it's a disaster.
I'll finish last.
- That looks good.
- Gosh.
How do I make curry?
(She becomes curious after all this time.)
Is curry supposed to be...
Hey, Hae Joon. For curry,
is this too watery?
- Well, it's...
- What do you think?
- Add some powder.
- Okay.
- It'll thicken right away.
(And to make up for the lack of flavours...)
(Honey?)
(Behind Chef Yum's back)
- Do you not like yours?
- I'm all good.
If you worry, the food absorbs your worries.
- I'm relaxed.
- You're right.
- I'm really enjoying this.
- Me too.
(White Spoon might lose their jobs.)
It's...
- Hae Joon.
- Yes?
Come here for a second.
Judge, will you excuse us?
We need to discuss something.
Hae Joon, taste it, and tell me...
how I can revive it. This doesn't taste as I expected.
(Joons tries Auntie Curry's curry.)
- What should I do?
- What did you add?
I just cooked the way I normally do.
Add more salt.
- Salt?
- Yes, salt.
(Prescribing salt this time)
(She tastes it again.)
(Disappointed)
(Tasting it)
(Seasoning again)
(Tasting it again)
(Again)
(Staring)
Aren't you full now?
Are you having a meal by yourself?
(That's not it.)
(She keeps tasting it.)
What is this flavour?
(What is this flavour?)
I won't eat it either.
(Sighing)
I put my soul into it.
(The finished curry is submitted in two bowls...)
(for Chef Yum and the public panel.)
- Nothing I can do now. That's it.
- Why did we try so hard?
I'm nervous now.
(The participants are about to be judged.)
Their curries look good.
Yoon Seo's curry looks tasty.
They all look different.
- Is 50 the perfect score for me?
- Yes.
(Scoring system: Total 100 points, Chef Yum: 50 points,)
(Public panel of 5: 50 points, 10 points each)
(We'll begin judging.)
Hello, I'm Auntie Curry.
My curry is the homemade curry from the 1990s.
It has a texture from apples and flavours from the cheese.
Okay.
That's what it is.
I'll try it. After tasting it,
I'll evaluate it. You can go back now.
(Stop crying.)
I think I'm going to cry.
(The first participant feels like crying for some reason.)
I'll have a little bit of everything at once.
(Chef Yum prepares to taste it.)
(She savours it carefully.)
(Nervous)
(Was Auntie Curry able...)
She's so serious.
(to satisfy Chef Yum's palate?)
(While it tastes a little funky, it's made with care.)
(White Spoon Auntie Curry: 39 points out of 50 points)
- Hello, I'm Do You Know Hidden.
- Okay.
(What is the secret hidden in her curry?)
My secret weapons are coffee powder...
and a spoonful of yuzu marmalade.
I added lots of cabbage,
so it's sweet and flavourful.
I see. I love cabbage.
Though it's the first curry I've made,
I'd say I'm pretty satisfied with it.
- Okay. I got it.
- Thank you.
(Tasting the novice chef's first curry)
(She can't breathe from nervousness she had never felt before.)
I'm nervous.
(The judge savours the curry slowly.)
She's tasting it for way too long.
(She's thinking longer than she did for Auntie Curry's.)
(Having a headache)
She's having a hard time.
(After much deliberation, she leaves a verdict.)
(Do You Know Hidden: The first curry she's ever made)
(She created harmony with various ingredients,)
(but the meat doesn't blend well.)
(Current Ranking 1st, Auntie Curry, 39 points)
(1st, Do You Know Hidden, 40 points)
(Do You Know Hidden takes 1st place by 1 point.)
It's hot.
- It's hot.
- Gosh. Hurry.
(Next participant appears while causing a little scene.)
(Indian Matfia's curry with its deep, rich colour)
- Hello, this is Indian Matfia.
- Hello.
It's a curry made with a lot of love.
You'll know once you taste it.
I won't say much. I'll let the flavour speak for itself.
All right.
(His confidence puts the other competitors on edge.)
Jung Ah is taking it very seriously.
(Is his confidence actually backed by something?)
(She smiles.)
Jung Ah just smiled.
(Really?)
(Did she really smile?)
(Anticipating)
(Indian Matfia: Trembling hands, meticulous planning)
(The curry has a great depth of flavour,)
(but I wish the potatoes were a little more cooked.)
You Seok's score is out.
(A high score of 43 out of 50)
(Current Ranking)
(Pulling ahead of Do You Know Hidden and taking the 1st place)
(Will he manage to hold on to 1st place until the end?)
- It's the last one.
- It's the last dish.
(Today's final curry chef)
Hello.
This is Joons.
Was it Victoria Joons? It was something Joons.
- Dumpling Joons.
- Was it Navilela Joons?
- It's Ravioli.
- "Ravioli."
Plump Ravioli.
(This is Plump Ravioli With Joons.)
This is...
Plump Ravioli Curry.
- Okay.
- Yes.
The Korean melon side dish helps cleanse your palate...
and balance out the strong flavours.
It's a bold dish.
You'll be surprised when you taste it.
It looks really unusual.
I'll eat them together.
(She prepares to taste it carefully.)
I feel nervous.
(Chef Yum takes a big bite of one dumpling.)
(Dropping his head)
(Nodding)
She just nodded her head.
She hasn't nodded once until now.
(A bite of Plump Ravioli With Joons' Korean melon side dish)
(Will his bold move work?)
(The dumplings and curry work really well together.)
(The best one)
(The Korean melon is great too.)
(Chef Yum's verdict: It's the best one.)
I just want to avoid placing last.
(Current Ranking)
(Plump Ravioli With Joons takes 1st place confidently.)
(1st place, Plump Ravioli With Joons, 45 points)
The panellists should eat more comfortably.
(Meanwhile, the public panel is also evaluating.)
The number two curry was...
(The public panel's score will also impact the final 1st place.)
We have to add up the scores, right?
(The participants watch anxiously.)
The die has been cast.
I'm so nervous.
(Who will be the winner in this fierce showdown?)
The scores were really tight.
- By a narrow margin?
- It was very competitive.
(The final results are finally here.)
I'll start by announcing third place.
(The first ranking announced is third place.)
- In third place...
- I'm curious.
- With a score of 76 points.
- A score of 76?
Do You Know Hidden.
Yoon Seo placed third?
(Underdog, Do You Know Hidden)
- Yoon Seo placed third?
- Hurry up and announce it.
Yoon Seo's curry was so good.
Yoon Seo placed third?
- Hurry up and announce it.
- Yoon Seo's curry was so good.
Please announce it already.
(Do You Know Hidden, a total of 76 points)
(4.5 stars on something you'd buy at a restaurant)
It's disappointing, but at least I didn't come in last.
I'll announce the second place.
- It's disappointing.
- In second place...
- I hope I'm in second place.
- But I didn't come in last.
A score of 78 points.
The score difference is only two.
Indian Matfia.
(Indian Matfia, a total of 78 points)
(Chef Yum: 43 points, Public panel: 35 points)
Hae Joon must've placed first.
- No, I don't think so.
- Or is it Sun Young?
(Plump Ravioli With Joons collapses with anxiety.)
(Curry Showdown's Current Ranking)
(2. Indian Matfia: 78, 3. Do You Know Hidden: 76)
Only the 1st and 4th place remain.
One of you placed first, and one of you placed last.
(Joons ran around tirelessly and gave his all.)
(Meanwhile, Auntie Curry aimed for bonus points.)
(But the unexpected taste left her feeling uneasy.)
The 1st place earned 79 points.
(Chef Yum's score 45 points versus 39 points)
(Who will be the winner of the curry showdown?)
In 1st place, Auntie Curry.
(Auntie Curry turns the tables.)
(Plump Ravioli With Joons places last.)
(My entire life as a chef is falling apart.)
(Plump Ravioli With Joons, a total of 69 points)
(Chef Yum: 45 points, Public panel: 24 points)
I just wanted to avoid coming in last.
(Public panel's verdict: The dumplings are salty.)
(It makes me crave more rice.)
(Auntie Curry, a total of 79 points)
(Chef Yum: 39 points, Public panel: 40 points)
(Public panel's verdict: It's smooth and familiar.)
(A perfect combination of apples and cheese)
This is unbelievable.
Thank you.
(An unexpected twist completely defied expectations.)
I will work even harder from now on.
(Sorrow, joy)
Seriously.
I can't believe it.
I got goosebumps on my face.
- That's so funny.
- I will never...
make curry in my life.
(His clothes and spirit are both in tatters.)
Isn't this wild rock seaweed that's known to be expensive?
- Thank you so much.
- I'm so jealous.
How much would that cost?
It's what we harvested.
- Thank you.
- Congratulations.
(A meaningful Fresh off the Sea gift)
Congratulations.
- Let's eat.
- Let me try the number one curry.
Everyone, this is the number one curry.
Please give it a try.
You gave me a lot of rice.
There's no kimchi.
(Everyone shares Auntie Curry's 1st-place curry.)
It's delicious.
- You could've placed 2nd.
- I should've placed 2nd.
(Humming)
The savoury flavour of the cheese...
captivated many people.
It's good.
(A curry worthy of taking first place)
Mine is my favourite.
What caused the failure? Is it the dumpling?
(One man is still trying to figure out what went wrong.)
Mine has...
a horrible aftertaste.
(Laughing)
The dumpling flavour is way too strong.
- It overpowers everything.
- That's important.
The dumplings take over the whole dish.
(Listen carefully and take notes)
My favourite is Hae Joon's.
(Shocked)
For me, it had the lightest taste.
(Feeling bitter)
(Let's see.)
(Sun Young serves 3 different curries in 1 bowl.)
It's incredible.
(What is it?)
It tastes the best when the three are mixed together.
Except Hae Joon's.
It's just like Fresh off the Sea.
When we're alone, we may not shine,
but when we come together...
I hope the three of you blend well together.
(Oops)
(It's an unintended roast.)
- You're so funny, Sun Young.
- Then our curry...
I'm never...
coming back here again.
(Declaring a boycott against Fresh off the Sea)
It's perfect for the show. I mean...
What is he saying?
It's in line with the concept of the show.
Let's have another cooking showdown.
Yes, I like the idea.
- Don't you agree?
- Yes.
- This is so much fun.
- I'm confident I can win next time.
You'll make another dish.
- Let's make another dish.
- What's the dish?
I figured out everyone's taste.
Hae Joon, do it with us one more time.
- You should come back.
- Come on, Hae Joon.
(Will Hae Joon get his chance at redemption in a rematch?)
Just one more time.
(We look forward to their next adventure that's coming soon.)
(One month later in Taean)
(Today,)
(you're heading to...)
(a rock festival being held in Taean.)
(Screaming with excitement)
(That's awesome.)
(Rock?)
(Can we watch the concerts?)
(A rock festival all of a sudden?)
(We'll give you a hint.)
(Bring out the hint.)
(Suddenly, a red carpet appears.)
(Confused)
(I hear music.)
(They have no idea, but they're excited anyway.)
(Do we have a guest today?)
(A rocker?)
(A rocker is coming to Fresh off the Sea?)
(The second guest, Cho Jung Seok)
(Screaming)
(It's hard to believe that Cho Jung Seok is on this show!)
(This vast, wide-open place is...)
(Taean, South Chungcheong Province, with rich mudflat resources)
(Manila clams are pure rock too!)
(The Siblings' Manila Clam Festival will take place.)
(The siblings made their debut as Manila clam rockers.)
(They can't stop shaking it.)
(Manila clams are pure rock too.)
(Manila clams are pure joy?)
(The guest singer on the show, Cho Jung Seok)
(Jung Ja, Jung Seok's alter ego on Fresh off the Sea)
(When an older member sings,)
(the youngest member sings along.)
(When the oldest member starts a role play,)
(the guest plays along with her.)
(They can't stop laughing, thanks to Jung Seok.)
(Everyone falls for Jung Seok, the lucky charm.)
(They fall into the mud too.)
(It's time to fall for the siblings' food.)
(Siblings' Chinese Restaurant is now open.)
(The table will be packed with the finest Chinese cuisine.)
(It's better than the dishes at Chinese restaurants.)
(This Chinese restaurant serves great food.)
(He instantly falls in love.)
(The oldest member is satisfied.)
(It's so delicious that he starts singing.)
(Come check out the exciting Siblings' Chinese Restaurant.)